<TravellerCampaign active="True" name="The Ellis Campaign">
  <Description>Ellis' first campaign in the world of role playing. </Description>
  <Referee>Simon 'Code God' Snowden. </Referee>
  <StartDate>12/03/2015</StartDate>
  <Setting>The Third Imperium with a bit of a twist. </Setting>
  <Log>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="261/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Three days out in the wilderness sees Kfouzzor killed by what appears to be an imperial trooper working with the Vagr. He seems to pull him to the ground and then start biting him. Through Kfouzzor's sacrifice the hunters are distracted long enough for Fletch, Sam and Gvourdzon to get away. Breaking out of the forest they come across a mining camp - a mining camp with a strong security. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The team witnessed the infection of Kfouzzor by the one of the vampire's. Their bite allowing for a transmission of the nano phage responsible for transmitting the instructions of the alien into the brain of the host being. 

The camp they find themselves in is one of Sternmetal's and is where they hide the Wolblutn whilst Banerji is supposedly in the Vagr Extents. This is a possible way off planet for what remains of the team. entering Giilaan has arrived in system and this provides a useful exit strategy for the team - if Fletch can see it. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="258/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>On arrival they head immediately to the governor's mansion where the Sternmetal representatives are staying. Outside the team runs in to trouble where Roman's wise cracking ways wind up the tense soldiers. Secured they witness an exchange between a Vagr and junior offices as he tries to tell them of an impending attack by Vagr corsairs. Led to the colonel in charge they are too late as the attack starts - and unexpectedly Fletch executes both the colonel and Banerji. Soldiers misunderstanding the situation spray the room with Bullets. Julian and Roman are seriously injured and are left at a hospital. Fletch, Sam and a wounded Gvourdzon head out into the wilderness to avoid capture. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>Kuforuzeng members scent Gvourdzon and are keen to capture him and obtain the missing brooch with its critical message. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="257/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>The team land planet side and buy flights to the troubled region to confront Banerji. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The vampires have already linked up with the Vagr corsairs and have moved up the operation to spark a world war. One more step to ignite conflict across the subsector. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="256/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>The usual messing around with regards to off loading cargo and passengers. Against Fletch's better judgement they head for the Worldview lounge where they had their altercation with the Vertreibie. Here Fletch spots a news item, nothing really of interest in it until he spots Banerji. And now he wants to go planet side and confront his nemesis.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>275/1105 - Mortgage Due
Banerji has been roped in to act on behalf of Sternmetal whilst he is on overlay waiting for the time he can 'reappear' with the Lanthenum from the Vagr Extents.</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="255/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive at orbiting startport </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>Fun lies ahead on the planets surface.</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="252/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive at Aramanx system</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The vampires have arrived ahead of them. Besides Frome they have other business, they are linking up with the Kofurozeng in a plot to spark war in the subsector to cover up their wider agenda. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="238/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Jump to Aramanx </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="235/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive Pavvane spaceport.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="232/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive Pavanne </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="218/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive at Nasemin spaceport </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="215/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive Nasemin. One more reveal from Julian as they head in system. Frome is from Aramanx.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>But he is not there. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="208/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Towers, refuel and straight jump to Nasemin. Julian has some news on the evidence from Dagiran. There is evidence of augments from the attacker, nano technology. and the name Jonathan Frome is linked to the missing pages.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The augments are some left over nano machines from the alien hardware infecting the trooper who attacked the lab staff. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="201/1105 ">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Jumping to Towers, refuel and straight jump to Nasemin </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The vampires know that it is Jonathan Frome and have already headed for Aramanx on his trail. Frome is an space and dimension manipulator able to bend and move through space and different dimensions. The vampires are after him to open up a portal in to their own dimension. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="198/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>The crew broke into the crime scene and found evidence the police had missed. They picked up a book with torn out pages, some physical evidence Julian had hidden and a partial badge from a military uniform. An imperium logo with a blood red crown on it. Further investigation may have uncovered something. About the time covering the missing pages Dagiran had been working on papers about Psionic indviduals who may be able to bend space and dimensions. Sam also discovered that similar murders had been committed before the team had arrived clearing them. But also that the LBS was in port.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>The murders have been committed by a nest of alien nanoware infested vampires. They are all members of a special operations group from the Aramis Colonial fleet travelling in an LBS. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="197/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> When Dagran didn't make contact the next day Roman and Julian went to his office to see what was going on. What they found was a huge shock. The whole of Dagiran's team had been ripped apart by what looked like animals. Julian and Roman were held by the police for questioning after some inappropriate comments from Roman. After hours of questioning they were released but not allowed back to the March Harrier. Sam and the rest were also removed and put up in a hotel. Fletch and Gvourdzon were hospitalised for tests that confirmed part of the story by Roman.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>dagiran and the lab staff have been attacked by the alien infected troopers. Their master is a noble of the Aramis noble family. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="196/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Dagiran reports back that the issue is with the Anolas affecting the two crew members and that they could return to the March Harrier whilst he conducted further research and would contact them in the morning. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>It is now clear that the anoles are responsible for the teams fading intellects. Now distance fro the anolas will allow them to recover. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="195/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Julian took them to the University of Junidy psychology dept where they met with Professor Dagiran. Clearly and Julian and Dagiran had some history between them. Later Julian spilled the beans about his Psionic abilities and that was how he and Dagiran knew him. He was however close lipped about why Dagiran was cold towards him. Dagiran was happy to help Fletch and Gvourdzon.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>Dagiran knows of Julian's experiments on the Zhodani prisoners. He also knows of Julian's psychic powers and is suspicious of his motives. He knows he worked for the Imperium, but knows little more. </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="194/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>  In orbit around Junidy.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="191/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Jump in to Junidy jump point. Julian realises that the credit chip can be hacked, but is going to require biometric data from the agent. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="182/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Fly in to Towers, straight to the gas giant, refule, then on to Junidy. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="172/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Back at the starport. Julian starts hacking the money chips.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>It requires biometric input to make the transfer.  </LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="170/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Medal ceremony.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="165/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive in the capital city</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="164/1105 ">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Barricade ambush</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="161/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>As they traverse through the countryside they come to a canyon where they are once more ambushed. Deadman's Canyon lives up to its name and a number of the troops die in a hail of fire. Fletch crawls inexplicably beneath the chairs of the vehicle he is in and takes little part in the action. Sam, Gvourdzon and Roman join the troops in returning fire on the terrorists. Unfortunately Roman takes a number of hits and succumbs to his wounds passing out. Gvourdzon takes a fair few hits as well and although injured, Sam receives only minor injuries. Under the chair, Fletch appears to be fine, although a little confused about the whole affair.
Exiting the canyon harried by fire they spot a military convoy that comes to their assistance and chase the remaining terrorists away....</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="160/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> The train comes to a halt and when the team got off the train to see what was happening they found some of the Count's troops gathered around a tree that had appeared to have fallen across the tracks. But as Roman and Gvourdzon investigate an explosion goes off behind the train trapping it. As the troops and the team wonder what is happening a group of terrorists opened fire. In the ensuing firefight a number of the count's troops lose their lives and so do many more terrorists. Fortunately the team receive minor injuries. Sam does discover an interesting pendant on each of the dead terrorists, a heart with a ring of thorns piercing it.
Having rid themselves of the terrorists the troops tend to their wounded and retrieve vehicles from the train carriages. They load the crates on to the vehicles, the team join the remaining troops and they once more set off, now across country, towards the capital city.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="159/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> The train stops at a retreat just as they get into the mountains. A scientist type guy comes aboard the train and removes one of the crates from the train. After a couple of hours the train set off once more. The team suspect that the Anolas are affecting Fletch and if he is separated from them he suffers ill effects.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="158/1105 ">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Count Ibrahim Radge arrives in his train to pick up the cargo. He refuses to give the team the payment until the cargo is taken to the capital. Fletch lost it during negotiations and began saying some bizarre things. Fortunately G'vourdzon was on hand to save the day. It was eventually agreed that Fletch, Sam, Roman and Gvourdzon would travel with the Count's group and act as extra protection. The next day the train set off.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="156/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive at Yebab.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="154/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive in Yebab.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="143/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Passengers Delivered to Nasemin, Mortgage paid.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="118/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Cargo Delivered to Pavanne.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="111/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Cargos delivered and an ultimatum.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="10/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Built up the March Harrier Armoury. Sorted cargos for Pavanne, and got a big deal to deliver 10 tons of cargo to Yebab.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="109/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Meet Giilaan, give the info about Bannerji. Gun battle in the Worldview bar, Fletch, Roman, and Gvourdzon injured. The Vriterbei know where Fletch is.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="106/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Arrive Aramanx. Mortgage Payment</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="083/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> However old man Oberlindes pays for the teams involvement in this fracas considering the role of his own crew. And then a deal is made to take him and his number 1 to Aramanx. Leave with Oberlinde and Allanroughul for Aramanx </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="082/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Waiting for new cargoes to be found and any other money making opportunities the team start drinking in a local bar. Here they find out some interesting gossip regarding the crash of the Mammoth on Aramis and talk to a local part engineer who worked alongside the original ship engineer and his incompetent replacement. Drink and loud mouths lead to a fight with the Akerut crew siding with the Ovberlindes crew. This leads to a night in chokey and what could have been an expensive night out.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="081/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Land Zila. A message awaits from Giilan that he will wait on Aramanx for them. They tell him they will be there for 110/1105.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="079/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> In to the Zila system. Paid Mortgage</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="072/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> The team have no intention of allowing Fletch to do the decent thing and rot on some backwater, so Roman and Gvourdzon return to the planets surface in the ships launch and breaching the church's seal in Ivetzny render unconscious the residents and carry Fletch along with his holy family to safety. Now time to show a clean pair of heals and get to Zila with a fresh cargo.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="068/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Their travails don't end once the team get back to Ivetzny. The priesthood are non too happy about the family of Anolas attaching themselves to the team especially Fletch. This holy family is too important for mere outsiders to mix with, but on consideration the head priest decides that Fletch will remain to care for the holy family whlct the rest of the team may leave.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="067/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> It takes a few days to reach a suitable area for logging the Howood trees, but once found they get to work. A few accidents with the low tech explosions leave Sam and Roman with splinters sticking out various parts of their body. Besides these alarming injuries the team are befriended by a family of Anola. It is these Anolas who first signal a coming disaster, but the team do not realise until a hungry carnivore leaps from the surrounding bushes and sets to trying to eat Fletch. Part comedy, part desperate melee ensues as the team tries to rescue Fletch from the clutches of this savage beast. By the time the beast flees Fletch is in a bad way and the team must pack up camp and leave with the Howood they have managed to gather so far.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="064/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Having bought their tickets to Ivetzny, they are looking to get their own wood. They prepare for the exhibition and board the train. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="062/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Arrive in system at Pysadi. Whilst unloading cargoes on the first day the team ponder Bannerji's activities. After an hour of trying to fathom Pysadi's computer system, Roman discovers a link between the wallet meassage on the Wolblutn flight plan. The team surmise that Bannerji is committing fraud by purchasing Lanthanum on Patanir, and then passing it of as coming from Scangen in the Vagr Extents for a higher price. The team send a mail to Eneri Giilaan hinting at their suspicions. Roman: -Hello, you may remember me, I'm from the team on Aramis who you discussed Bannerji with. We have information regarding his whereabouts and activities. Is the deal still on?. Awaiting reply.-</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="045/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Returning the body to star port the team are questioned and they report their suspicions. The authorities believe it to be pirates, but Fletch is convinced Bannerji is behind this atrocity. The team have another cargo and are now bound out of system heading for Pysadi, one of the places mentioned in Message to Bannerji.   Mortgage payment met. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="043/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Supplies delivered and on the return journey they pick up a distress signal. Following the signal they discover the stricken supply shuttle appearing to have taken a hit by nuclear munitions. On boarding they discover one of the crew in pieces, and the other barely alive. They bring him back the the March Harrier, but mortally wounded he dies with the name of a ship on his lips - the Wolblutn - Bannerji's free trader. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="037/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> A local broker approaches them asking them to deliver some supplies to prospectors after the supply shuttle goes missing. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="035/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> On arrival at Patinir they off load their cargo but soon discover trade is slow. The Imperium are holding Lanthanum prices low in the wake of a ship building programme and this is depressing all prospecting activities. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="21/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer> Land on Natoko, discharge passengers and freight sort payments out. Contacted by Ulrich who makes them a great offer and they accept it. The offer is of some installable fuel tanks that will extend the range of the March Herrier to 2 jumps without the need for refueling. This means the team can now break out of the Aramis Trace and avoid fall out from the museum caper and give all interested parties the slip. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="016/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Gvourdzon spills the beans from his perspective. He recounts his early days with the Kforuzeng Vagr corsair group and how factional infighting lead him to leave them for a smaller group, the Aegazeng. Here he acted as emissary between the two groups helping arbitrate disputes and collaborations. It is in this rule that he first encountered the brooches. The brooches were being used as communication devices between the Kforuzeng and other vroups, especially the mega corporation - Tukera. As the Kforuzeng expanded Gvourdzon saw the writing on the wall for his own progression, and so when the opportunity arose he grabbed one of the brooches and ran. By the time the team met up with him he was down on his luck. A fiddle with the brooch eventually led to uncovering a small indentation that could hide a slip of paper or memory sliver. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="012/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>The March Harrier loaded and Gvourdzon smuggled on board after some strange goings on with crates whilst getting through customs. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="012/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Pick up the ship.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="011/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Break-in at the Aramis Museum, steal The Brooch and find an interesting XBoat Message.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="009-11/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Chilling and preparing for the break-in</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="008/110">
      <LogEntryPlayer>JH and SF book into hotel opposite museum, the plan is sorted</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="007/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Gvourdzon feeling better after his beating and explains the situation, team work out a plan to get The Brooch from the museum.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="006/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>In morning Mine visit. Afternoon at the Aramis Museum. All the stuff with Gvourdzon.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="005/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Get 2 High Passage passengers and 1 middle passage. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="004/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Meeting with Eneri Giilaan. He claims to be a business associate of Bannerji who is owed money for past deals. Fletch is not convinced believing he has all the hall marks of law enforcement. Gilaan promises rewards for any information on Bannerji the team uncover. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="003/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Meal at the TAS on Bannerji after finding and returning his wallet. But when they go for the meal Bannerji has already left on his ship the Wolblutn. </LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="003/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Roman and Sam get a full load to Natoko (Freight Shipping). Fletch susses the underworld of Leedor</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="002/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Purchase The March Harrier.</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="001/1105">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Cellebration</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
    <LogEntry EntryDate="365/1104">
      <LogEntryPlayer>Fletch and Roman arrive at Leedor on Aramis, Sam and Julian muster out at the same time. Fletch is fleeing a rather discruntled criminal organisation on Rhylanor</LogEntryPlayer>
      <LogEntryReferee>?</LogEntryReferee>
    </LogEntry>
  </Log>
  <Assets>
    <Asset>
      <AssetName>Asset1</AssetName>
      <AssetDescription>The number 1asset</AssetDescription>
    </Asset>
    <Asset>
      <AssetName>Asset2</AssetName>
      <AssetDescription>The number 2asset</AssetDescription>
    </Asset>
    <Asset>
      <AssetName>Asset3</AssetName>
      <AssetDescription>The number 3asset</AssetDescription>
    </Asset>
    <Asset>
      <AssetName>Asset4</AssetName>
      <AssetDescription>The number 4asset</AssetDescription>
    </Asset>
  </Assets>
  <Notes>The Vampires

Jonathan Frome

Annic Nova

Eneri Giilaan

the Pirates of Drinax and Who is Julian Hillier?

The Fifth Frontier War

The Civil War

Forging New Frontiers and Making New Friends

Into the Unknown</Notes>
</TravellerCampaign>
